gowebguide.com 2018-05-15

# Go WebGuide | Human-Edited deep link directory - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Information Collection and Use

GoWebguide.com is the sole owner of the information collected from this site, if any. We respect the privacy of every individual who visits our website. Information submitted by a visitor or buyer will not be shared, sold, reused in lists, or be used for any other purpose than to complete a transaction or address a customer service concern. This Privacy Policy outlines the information we might collect and how we may use any information collected. This Policy will also instruct you what to do if you do not want your personal information collected when you visit our website. These policies are subject to change or revision. Any changes will be posted here. You should review this section regularly.

Collecting Information from Children

We have no intention of collecting any personal information from individuals under eighteen years of age. Where appropriate, we will specifically instruct children not to submit such information to our website. Should a child provide us with personally identifiable information, a parent or guardian of that child should contact us to request the child’s information be deleted from our records. We will use reasonable efforts to delete the child’s information from our existing files.

Personal Information

We will not collect your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address unless you provide it to us voluntarily. Should you provide us with any of this information. However, we may attempt to collect such information if we believe your use of this website violates any laws or our terms of use. If you do not want this information collected, please do not submit it to us.

If you have already submitted this information and would like for us to remove it from our records, please contact us. We will use reasonable efforts to delete your information from our files.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on a visitor’s hard drive containing information about the visitor. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. A cookie is used on our site only to keep track of a user’s session. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still browse our site but may encounter other than intended results. Most Internet Browsers allows you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions to learn more about these functions.

Log Files

In some cases, we may collect additional not personally identifiable information. Examples of this type of information may include the type of Internet browser and operating system you are using, and the URL of the website from which you entered our website. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, track visitor’s movements, and gather broad demographic and geographic information for aggregate use.

Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy, please [contact us.](http://gowebguide.com/contact.php)

Last Modified February, 2012
